Contact

Asaba, Delta State, Nigeria +2348130822108 (Mobile) greatedafeoke@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/edafe-oke-14bb23216 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Project Management Windows Skill Development

Edafe Oke

Software Engineer

Asaba, Delta State, Nigeria

Summary

A Full-stack Software Engineer with extensive experience in developing a wide range of digital solutions. While presenting a comprehensive list of all my skills is currently impractical, I've highlighted the most pertinent skills in today's dynamic market.

Back-End:

- Proficient in Python with frameworks like Flask, FastAPI.
- NodeJs expertise using Express.js and Next.js.
- Java and Kotlin proficiency with Android SDK.

Front-End:

- Strong command of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Familiarity with popular libraries and frameworks such as JQuery, Bootstrap, Typescript, React.js, Next.js and React native.

Mobile:

- Experience in mobile app development using React Native and Android SDK (Kotlin+Java).

Database:

- Database management expertise with MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL, OracleDB, and H2.

Other Skills:

- Familiarity with C, Open AI.
- Proficient in Restful API development and integration.
- Knowledge of various tools and services including Google Maps, Firebase, Git, CI/CD, Linux (Ubuntu), Digital Ocean, AWS.

Experience

Softalx Solutions

Mobile Application Developer

January 2020 - December 2023 (4 years)

Page 1 of 2

Asaba, Delta State, Nigeria

Created fast, seamless and reliable mobile applications, fixed bug, work well and communicated with other developers on the team

Upwork Upwork

June 2019 - February 2020 (9 months)

United States

Carried out freelancing jobs such as mobile app development, API building using flask (python) and FastAPI

ZenithTech Solutions
Mobile Application Developer
May 2016 - December 2017 (1 year 8 months)
Lagos State, Nigeria

In the bustling heart of technological innovation, my journey with Zenithtech Solutions as a Mobile Application Developer has been nothing short of exhilarating. Tasked with crafting cutting-edge mobile experiences, my role has been a dynamic blend of creativity, problem-solving, and staying ahead of the ever-evolving mobile landscape.

Education

Delta State Polytechnic, Ogwashi-Uku

Higher National Diploma, Computer Science · (January 2021 - November 2023)

ALX Academy

Software Engineering, Computer Science · (April 2020 - May 2021)

Delta state Polytechnic Ogwashi-uku National Diploma, Computer Science · (2018 - 2020)